Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection
Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection
- Box listing
  - Center for Adult Learning and Education Credentials (Box 21)
  - Center for Ecomomic and Social Information (Box 21)
  - CERES (Box 21)
  - Charters, Alexander N. (Box 21)
  - Comparative and International Education Society (CIES) (Box 21)
  - Coast Communicator (Box 21)
  - Collage (Box 21)
  - College of Agricultural Life Science (Box 21)
  - Community Education Journal (Box 21)
  - Commisssion on Higher Education (Box 21)
  - COMPAS (Box 21)
  - CONNECT (Box 21)
  - Contact with Denmark (Box 21)
  - Continuing Edition (Box 21)
  - Cornerstone (Box 21)
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit (CCEU) (Box 21)
  - Councilgram (Box 21)
  - Course trends in Adult Learning (Box 21)
  - Activity (ACT) (Box 22)
  - The Adult Educator (Box 22)
  - Adult Leadership (Box 22)
  - The Adult View (Box 22)
  - Affinities (Box 22)
  - Aging News (Box 22)
  - Agricultural News (Box 22)
  - ALBSU (Box 22)
  - ALL (Box 22)
  - The AC-UNU (Box 22)
  - American Medical Asociation (Box 22)
  - AMT Events (Box 22)
  - Asian South Pacific Bureau of A.E. (Box 22)
  - Association of Teacher Education (Box 22)
  - BCEL (Box 22)
  - Benchmark (Box 22)
  - Bulletin Publication by ICUAE (Box 22)
  - Bulletin of Continuing Education in International Affairs (Box 22)
  - Business Council Effective Literacy (Box 22)
  - Tel-Coms (Box 23)
  - Today (Box 23)
  - Tranet (Box 23)
  - UNDP (Box 23)
  - UNFPA Newsletter-Population (Box 23)
  - United Nations University of International Centre for Education (Box 23)
  - United Nations University, "Work in Progress" (Box 23)
  - University of Illinois at Urbana - Champaign Bulletin (Box 23)
  - University of Jamme (Box 23)
  - Vient de Paraitre (Box 23)
  - Vocational Education (Box 23)
  - Who Press (Box 23)
  - Whole Non-Profit Catalog (Box 23)
  - World Goodwill (Box 23)
  - Journal of the African Association for Literature (Box 24)
  - Journal of World Education (Box 24)
  - Kappan (Box 24)
  - Khitpen (Box 24)
  - Ladder (PLAN) (Box 24)
  - Learning in New York (Box 24)
  - L'ICEA (Box 24)
  - Lifelong Learning (Box 24)
  - Mass Media A.E. (Box 24)
  - Middle East Review (Box 24)
  - Middle States Association (Box 24)
  - Midwest Focus (Box 24)
  - Mississippi Community Education Quarterly (Box 24)
  - Momentum (Box 24)
  - NACAC (Box 25)
  - NALPS (Box 25)
  - National Council for International Visitors (NCIV) (Box 25)
  - National Info Exchange (Box 25)
  - National Institute of Adult Continuing Education (NIACE) (Box 25)
  - National Report (Box 25)
  - NATTS Network (Box 25)
  - News (Box 25)
  - News and Views (Box 25)
  - NN+Q (Box 25)
  - Norwegian Institute of Adult Education Reports (Box 25)
  - Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (Box 26)
  - Various Pamphlets (Box 26)
  - The Education Quarterly (Box 26)
  - Various Pamphlets (over 1/4 ") (Box 26)
  - Various large pamphlets (Box 27)
  - UNESCO (Box 28)
  - International (Box 28)
  - Peace Corps (Box 28)
  - International Corporation on Adult Education (Box 28)
  - How to Learn (Box 28)
  - Competency (Box 28)
  - Kellogg Project, Misc. Occasional Papers (Box 29)
  - Studies in Continuing Education (Box 29)
  - Misc. Adult Education at Syracuse University Directories (Box 29)
  - Association of University Evening Colleges (AUEC) (Box 30)
  - Fred Stamm (Box 30)
  - Brenton Stevenson, University of Toledo (Box 30)
  - John Waters (Box 30)
  - Alvord Boeck (Box 30)
  - Formative Years 1940-1950 (Box 30)
  - Lewis Froman, Russel Sage College (Box 30)
  - Edwin Spengler, Brooklyn College (Box 30)
  - Willis Reals (Box 30)
  - Royce West (Box 30)
  - Roland B. Posey (Box 30)
  - Bibliography (Box 30)
  - Willis T Spivey (Box 30)
  - Bibliography (Box 30)
  - Father Wirtenberger (Box 30)
  - George Parkinson (Box 30)
  - Georgia State College (Box 30)
  - John Dyer (Box 30)
  - Frank Neuffer (Box 30)
  - Richard Mumma (Box 30)
  - Henry Mills (Box 30)
  - Donald Miller (Box 30)
  - L.D. O'Neil (Box 30)
  - Doris O'Brian (Box 30)
  - Robert Love (Box 30)
  - Freld Research Letters (Box 30)
  - Leslie P. Hardy (Box 30)
  - Harry A. Cochran (Box 30)
  - A. Caswell Ellis (Box 30)
  - William R. Hockenberry (Box 30)
  - Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults (CSLEA) - Sandy (Box 30)
  - Dissertation correspondence (Box 30)
  - Introductions (Box 30)
  - Willim O'Regan (Box 30)
  - The Adult Basic Education (ABE) Curriculum and Its Development (Box 30)
  - Life Planning with Adults (Box 30)
  - Libraries and Literacy Education (Box 30)
  - Education for Senior Adults (Box 30)
  - A Decade for Development (ASPA) (Box 30)
  - Films of the United Nations Family (Box 30)
  - Resources in Migrant Education (Box 30)
  - Selected bibliographies on Culture (Box 30)
  - Bibliography of Publishers (Box 30)
  - Syracuse Scholar, vol. 8, Sp. 1987 (Box 30)
  - Georgia State (Box 30)
  - Personalite Education Societe (Box 30)
  - Resources, Print: Misc. Directories (Box 31)
  - Education, Higher Finance (Box 31)
  - Resources, Print: Misc. (Box 31)
  - Resources, Print: Council of Europe, 3 volumes (Box 31)
  - Media: 2 Misc. Pamphlets (Box 31)
  - Data Base Systems (Box 31)
  - Professional Resumes: Misc. Directories (Box 31)
  - National Adult Education Boards, Councils, etc. (Box 31)
  - Professional Development (Box 31)
  - Agencies, Misc. (Box 31)
  - Evaluation of Support Services: UNISIST (Box 32)
  - Availability/Accessibility of Support Services (Box 32)
  - Public Welfare (Box 32)
  - Environment-Bibliography-Adult Education Projects (Box 32)
  - International-Argentina (Box 32)
  - International-Australia (Box 32)
  - International-Austria (Box 32)
  - International-Botswana (Box 32)
  - Unpublished International Occasional Papers in Adult Education (Box 32)
  - International History of Adult Education (Box 32)
  - International Adult Education (Box 32)
  - International-Austalia (Box 33)
  - International-Brazil (Box 33)
  - International-Canada (Box 33)
  - International-Canada (Box 34)
  - International-Canada (Box 35)
  - International-Canada (Box 36)
  - International-Chile (Box 36)
  - International-China (Box 36)
  - International-Czechoslovakia (Box 36)
  - International-Denmark (Box 36)
  - International-France (Box 36)
  - International-Egypt (Box 36)
  - International-Estonia (Box 36)
  - International-Ethiopia (Box 36)
  - International-Finland (Box 36)
  - International-Germany (Box 36)
  - International-Ghana (Box 36)
  - International-Greece (Box 36)
  - International-Guyana (Box 36)
  - International-India (Box 36)
  - International-Iran (Box 36)
  - International-Ireland (Box 36)
  - International-Israel (Box 36)
  - International-Italy (Box 36)
  - International-Jamaica (Box 36)
  - International-Japan (Box 36)
  - International-Kenya (Box 36)
  - International-Korea (Box 36)
  - International-Malawi (Box 37)
  - International-Martinique (Box 37)
  - International-Mexico (Box 37)
  - International-Netherlands (Box 37)
  - International-Nigeria (Box 37)
  - International-New Zealand (Box 37)
  - International-Norway (Box 37)
  - International-Philippines (Box 37)
  - International-Poland (Box 37)
  - International-Portugal (Box 37)
  - International-Quatar (Box 37)
  - International-Romania (Box 37)
  - International-Singapore (Box 37)
  - International-South Africa (Box 37)
  - International-Sri Lanka (Box 37)
  - International-Sudan (Box 37)
  - International-Sweden (Box 37)
  - International-Switzerland (Box 37)
  - International-Tanzania (Box 37)
  - International-Thailand (Box 37)
  - International-Trinidad (Box 38)
  - International-Turkey (Box 38)
  - International-U.S.S.R. (Box 38)
  - International-United Kingdom (Box 38)
  - International-Venezuela (Box 38)
  - International-Yugoslavia (Box 39)
  - International-Zambia (Box 39)
  - International-Zimbabwe (Box 39)
  - International-Commonwealth (Box 39)
  - Education Journalism (Box 39)
  - Education-Exceptional Children, "The Open University" (Box 39)
  - Education of Minorities (Box 39)
  - Intercultural Education (Box 39)
  - Education-Environmental, Agricultural (Box 39)
  - European Centre for Development of Vocational Training (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: ASPBAE (Box 39)
  - Caribbean Regional Council for Adult Education (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: Commission of the European Communities (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: Commonwealth Secretariat (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: Council of Europe (Box 40)
  - Council of Europe: Education Directories (Box 40)
  - Comparative and International Education Society (CIES) (Box 40)
  - European Bureau for Development of Vocational Training (Box 40)
  - European Bureau of Adult Education-Education Legislation (Box 40)
  - European Community (Box 40)
  - International Baccalaureate Office (Box 40)
  - AAAE Adult Education News (Box 40)
  - AC-UNU Newsletter (Box 40)
  - Academy News (Box 40)
  - Accreditation (Box 40)
  - Activity (Box 40)
  - Adult and Continuing Education Today (Box 40)
  - Adult Education Clearinghouse (Box 40)
  - Adult Education Newsletter (Box 40)
  - Adult Literacy and Basic Skills Unit (Box 40)
  - AES Journal on Postsecondary Education (Box 41)
  - Agency for Instructional Television Newsletter (Box 41)
  - AICS Compass (Box 41)
  - Aid Highlight (Box 41)
  - Alfalit (Box 41)
  - AMA Continuing Medical Education Fact Sheet (Box 41)
  - Continuing Medical Education Newsletter (Box 41)
  - COE Newsletter (Box 41)
  - COE New trends (Box 41)
  - COMBASE: Newsletter/Community-based programs that work (Box 41)
  - Commission of Professors of Adult Education of AEA of USA Newsletter (Box 41)
  - Commonwealth News (Box 41)
  - Community Colleges for International Development-International News (Box 41)
  - Community Education Journal (Box 41)
  - Community Education Today (Box 41)
  - Community Services; CATALYST (Box 41)
  - Comparative Adult Education Newsletter (Box 41)
  - Continuing Educator (SACEM) (Box 41)
  - Continuing Education (Box 41)
  - Converging Trends (Box 41)
  - Cornell International Agriculture Monograph (Box 41)
  - CRESST Evaluation Comment (Box 41)
  - CSE Evaluation Comment (Box 41)
  - DAE Newsletter (Box 42)
  - Development Communication Report (Box 42)
  - EDUCAFRICA (Box 42)
  - Education for Aging News (Box 42)
  - Education for Tomorrow's Environment (Box 42)
  - Education Record (Box 42)
  - Engineering Industry Training Board Information Paper (Box 42)
  - Engineering Training Today (Box 42)
  - European Bureau of Adult Education: Newsletter (Box 42)
  - International-Finnish Adult Education Organizations (Box 42)
  - Five Minutes with ACHE (Box 42)
  - Focus Bulletin (Box 42)
  - For the Record (Box 42)
  - Ford Foundation Letter (Box 42)
  - Georgia Center Quarterly (Box 42)
  - Interlit (Box 42)
  - International Associates Newsletter (Box 42)
  - International Bureau of Education: Awareness List (Box 42)
  - Journal of World Education (Box 42)
  - KENYA Journal of Adult Education (Box 42)
  - L'ICEA (Box 42)
  - Labor Education (Box 42)
  - Learning (Box 42)
  - Learning Connection (Box 42)
  - Learning in New York (Box 42)
  - Lifelong Learning Forum (Box 43)
  - Linking the National Voluntary Sector (Box 43)
  - Listen Real Loud-News of Women's Liberation Worldwide (Box 43)
  - Media and Adult Learning (Box 43)
  - Memo (Box 43)
  - Mountain Plains Adult Education Newsletter (Box 43)
  - NACAC Bulletin (Box 43)
  - NEAP Newsletter (Box 43)
  - NAPCAE Exchange (Box 43)
  - National Center for Education Brokering Newsletter (Box 43)
  - National Council for International Visitors (NCIV) (Box 43)
  - National Report for Training and Development (Box 43)
  - National Report on Human Resources (Box 43)
  - NATTS News (Box 43)
  - Network Circuit (Box 43)
  - Network Exchange (Box 43)
  - Network Fact Sheet (Box 43)
  - Network Vanguard (Box 43)
  - International-New Zealand Journal of Adult Learning (Box 43)
  - News and Views (Box 43)
  - Newsounds (Box 43)
  - NFE Exchange (Box 43)
  - NHSC Bulletin (Box 43)
  - NHSC News (Box 43)
  - Non-Formal Education Bulletin (Box 43)
  - International-Norwegian Institute of Adult Education Reports (Box 43)
  - Notes and Studies (Box 43)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) Continuing Education News (Box 43)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) Newsletter (Box 43)
  - NYACCE (Box 43)
  - Office on Education Credit and Credentials News (Box 43)
  - Orbit (Box 44)
  - PACE-Paragraphs About Continuing Education (Box 44)
  - Participatory Research Newsletter (Box 44)
  - Peace Newsletter (Box 44)
  - Planned Parenthood World Population (Box 44)
  - POPULI (Box 44)
  - Programme News (Box 44)
  - Pulse (Box 44)
  - R&D for Higher Education (Box 44)
  - Re:ACE Reader (Box 44)
  - Region X: X Change (Box 44)
  - Release (Box 44)
  - Second Thoughts (Box 44)
  - SEVA-MANDIR Newsletter (Box 44)
  - Software Consortium (Box 44)
  - Spencer Foundation (Box 44)
  - State Association Newsletter (Box 44)
  - State Education Department (Box 44)
  - State Education Leader (Box 44)
  - Statements and Speeches (Box 44)
  - Studies of Higher Education and Research (Box 44)
  - International-Swedish National Board of Universities and Colleges (Box 44)
  - International-Swedish Research on Higher Education (Box 44)
  - Teaching Adults (Box 44)
  - Teaching at a Distance (Box 44)
  - Techniques for Teaching Adults (Box 44)
  - Theory, Innovation, and Practice in Andragogy (Box 44)
  - Transitions (Box 44)
  - Un Nuevo Dia (Box 44)
  - United Nations Population Policy Compendium (Box 44)
  - UNESCO Adult Education (Box 44)
  - UNESCO Backgrounder (Box 45)
  - UNESCO Educational Innovation and Information (Box 45)
  - UNESCO Facts and Figures (Box 45)
  - UNESCO Institute for Education Bibliography (Box 45)
  - UNESCO Surveys and Studies (Box 45)
  - UNESCO Unisist Newsletter (Box 45)
  - UNESCO-UNEP Environmental Education Newletter: CONNECT (Box 45)
  - UNFPA Newsletter-Population (Box 45)
  - UNU Newsletter (Box 45)
  - UNU Work in Progress (Box 45)
  - Vocational Educator (Box 45)
  - Vocational Training (Box 45)
  - Voices for Peace (Box 45)
  - Volunteer Voice (Box 45)
  - Worker's Education Association (WEA) News Journal of Workers Educational Association (Box 45)
  - Worker's Education Association (WEA) Women's Studies Newsletter (Box 45)
  - West Africa Crier-Newsletter of the Subregion: AALAE (Box 45)
  - Women's World (Box 45)
  - World Education Report (Box 45)
  - Worldlit Newsletter of World Literacy of Canada (Box 45)
  - News Education for Aging (Box 45)
  - Conferences, Meetings, and Symposiums (Box 45)
  - Statements on Adult Education by Council of Europe, Germany, and Canada (Box 45)
  - Information Census (Box 45)
  - Accreditation-CEU (Box 45)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) (Box 45)
  - Adult Education Administration (Box 46)
  - Bibliography (Box 46)
  - Agencies, Organizations, and Sponsors Civic Literacy (Box 46)
  - Community Education (Box 46)
  - Finances: Budgets, Grants and Funding Foundations (Box 46)
  - Finances (Box 46)
  - Evaluation (Box 46)
  - Counseling (Box 46)
  - Competency Based Adult Education (CBAE) Futures (Box 46)
  - History (Box 46)
  - Instruction (Box 46)
  - Community Education (Box 46)
  - Competency Based Adult Education (CBAE) (Box 46)
  - Michigan State University, Study Team Reports on Non-Formal Education (Box 46)
  - Labor Education Libraries (Box 47)
  - Libraries: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 47)
  - Literacy and English as a Second Language (Box 47)
  - Media Instruction: Extension Education through Television (Box 47)
  - Organizational Papers, Misc. (Box 47)
  - Gerontology: Older Adult Learner (Box 47)
  - Museums: An Overview of Museums and Continuing Education (Box 48)
  - Women-Education (Box 48)
  - Federal Agencies (Box 48)
  - State Agencies (Box 48)
  - (ACHE) Association for Continuing Higher Education (Box 48)
  - Adminstration (Box 48)
  - Administration Principles (Box 49)
  - Adult Finances (Box 49)
  - Adult Education-U.S. Agencies (Box 49)
  - Adult Agencies: International (Box 49)
  - Agencies: Non Governmental (Box 49)
  - Education Testing Service (Box 49)
  - NYACCE (Box 49)
  - Education Adult Instruction Methods (Box 49)
  - Education Minorities (Box 49)
  - Adult Education Association of the U.S. (Box 49)
  - Education Adult Evaluation (Box 50)
  - Instruction Methods (Box 50)
  - Community Agencies (Box 50)
  - Charitable Foundations (Box 50)
  - U.S. Professional Agencies (Box 50)
  - Public Schools (Box 50)
  - Dropouts (Box 50)
  - Non Governmental Universities and Colleges (Box 51)
  - Phyical Education (Box 51)
  - Administration Superintendents (Box 51)
  - Communication (Box 51)
  - Indian Education (Box 51)
  - Worker's Education Association (WEA) (Box 51)
  - Elementary Education (Box 51)
  - Education of Migrants (Box 51)
  - Religion (Box 51)
  - National Asssociation of Secondary Schools' Principals (Box 51)
  - Administration (Box 51)
  - Instruction Materials (Box 52)
  - Facilities (Box 52)
  - Peace Corps (Box 52)
  - Clearinghouse Adell (Box 52)
  - Institute for Instruction Methods: Stanford University (Box 52)
  - ERIC (Box 52)
  - Adult Organizations (Box 52)
  - Finances (Box 52)
  - U.S. Agencies (Box 52)
  - History (Box 52)
  - Legislation (Box 53)
  - National Advisory Council (Box 53)
  - Learning (Box 53)
  - Programs in Basic Education (Box 53)
  - Programs on Aging (Box 53)
  - Basic Education (Box 53)
  - International, Misc. Directories, 1980's (Box 53)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) (Box 53)
  - Education-Adult Higher: Misc. Pamphlets (Box 54)
  - Education-Adult Higher: Misc. Pamphlets (Box 55)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) in Mississippi (Box 56)
  - Niagara Falls Board of Education (Box 56)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 56)
  - Adult Programs on Aging (Box 56)
  - Agricultural Education (Box 56)
  - Bilingual and Bicultural Programs (Box 56)
  - Child Care Programs (Box 56)
  - Community Education (Box 57)
  - Conferences on Adult Education (Box 57)
  - International Conferences (Box 57)
  - Research Conference (Box 58)
  - Adult Education International Aid and Poverty Conference (Box 58)
  - Conference on ICUAE (Box 58)
  - International Symposium on Adult Education (Box 58)
  - International Council (Box 59)
  - First International Conference on Comparative Adult Ed (Box 59)
  - ICUAE Conference 1976 (Box 59)
  - 30th All India Adult Education Conference (Box 59)
  - Michigan State University Conferences: 1961, 67, 69, 76 (Box 59)
  - New York Association for Continuing Commmunity Education (Box 59)
  - Lifelong Learning Research Conference Proceedings (Box 59)
  - Adult Education Conference of North America, etc. (Box 59)
  - AEC Berkeley/Santa Barbara (Box 59)
  - AEC UNESCO (Box 60)
  - UNESCO Regional AEC (Box 60)
  - AEC - U.S. National Association Institution (Box 60)
  - U.S. National Groups Conferences (Box 60)
  - UNESCO Directions (Box 60)
  - Conference on Education and Occupational Needs of Asian-Pacific-American Women: National Institution of Education (Box 60)
  - Extension Education (Box 60)
  - Consumer Education (Box 60)
  - Cooperative Extension (Box 60)
  - Adult Correctional Education (Box 61)
  - Adult Literacy Responses to Comic Strip Narratives Among Inmates of a Correctional Institution (Box 61)
  - Opportunity Grants (Box 61)
  - Programs on Employment (Box 61)
  - English as a Second Language (Box 61)
  - Family Education (Box 61)
  - Family Education (Box 62)
  - Handicapped-Disadvantaged (Box 62)
  - Health Programs (Box 62)
  - Counseling (Box 62)
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education (Box 62)
  - The Learning Society (Box 63)
  - Higher Education (Box 63)
  - Directories on Adult Education Resources, Misc. (Box 63)
  - Directories on Adult Education Resources, Misc. (Box 64)
  - International Handbook for Resources for Education of Adults (Box 65)
  - Directories on Adult Education Resources, Misc. (Box 65)
  - Statistics (Box 65)
  - The Educational Characteristics of the American People (Box 65)
  - Pedagogical Reports (Box 65)
  - Adult Education Students (Box 65)
  - Adult Education Professional Teachers (Box 65)
  - Adult Education Teaching (Box 65)
  - Adult Education Teachers (Box 66)
  - Trends in Adult Education (Box 66)
  - Georgia Center Continued Education Acquisition Lists (Box 66)
  - University of Liverpool Acquisition Lists (Box 66)
  - Open University Acquisition Lists (Box 66)
  - NUFFIC-CESO Acquisition Lists (Box 67)
  - University of Reading Acquisition Lists (Box 67)
  - Training and Development (Box 67)
  - Lifelong Learning (Box 67)
  - Trends (Box 67)
  - World Education, Inc. (Box 67)
  - UNESCO (Box 67)
  - SCUTREA (Box 67)
  - Managing Adult Literacy Training (Box 67)
  - Fourth International Conference on Adult Education (Box 67)
  - Council of Europe (Box 67)
  - UNDP (Box 67)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 67)
  - University of British Columbia (Box 67)
  - A Source Book for Education and Vocational Counselors: "The Alive Directory" (Box 67)
  - Higher Adult Education Pamphlets, Misc. (Box 68)
  - Economics Education (Box 68)
  - Illiteracy (Box 68)
  - Labor (Box 68)
  - Lifelong Learning (Box 68)
  - Lifelong Learning (Box 69)
  - Literacy (Box 69)
  - Literacy Instruction (Box 69)
  - Occupational Programs (Box 69)
  - Aging Programs (Box 69)
  - Occupational and Vocational Education (Box 70)
  - Vocational Education (Box 70)
  - Parenting Programs (Teenagers, Hyperactive Children) (Box 70)
  - Professional Adult Educators (Box 70)
  - Professional (Box 70)
  - Conference-U.S. National Association Institution (Box 70)
  - Public Schools (Box 71)
  - Religion (Box 71)
  - Residential Programs (Box 71)
  - Training and Development at Syracuse University (Box 71)
  - ASTD Educational Programs (Box 71)
  - Programs for Women (Box 71)
  - Programs for Development (Box 71)
  - Educational Programs for Youth (Box 71)
  - NYACCE (Box 71)
  - Program Development (Box 71)
  - Program Development (Box 72)
  - ERIC on Research (Box 72)
  - Public Relations (Box 72)
  - Research in Adult Education: Misc. Pamphlets (Box 72)
  - Research in Adult Education: Misc. Pamphlets (Box 73)
  - Problem Solving (Box 74)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Reports (Box 74)
  - Pamphlets on Adult Education Research, Misc. (Box 74)
  - Problem Solving (Box 74)
  - Publications on Adult Education Research, Misc. (Box 74)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) Research Center (Box 75)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 75)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) Pamphlets and Publications International-World Education, Misc. (Box 76)
  - World Bank (Box 76)
  - European Centre for Development of Vocational Training (Box 76)
  - Comparative Education of Latin America: Costa Rica (Box 76)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 77)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 78)
  - Listing of Periodicals Received by Syracuse University (Box 78)